(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) When we're out in a crowd laughing loud
and nobody knows why When we're lost at
a club getting drunk and you give me
that smile Going home in the back of
a car and your hand touches mine When
we're done making love and you look up
and give me those eyes Cause all of
the small things that you do are what
remind me what I felt for you And
when we're apart and I'm missing you I
close my eyes and all I see is
you And the small things you do When
you call me at night while you're out
getting high with your friends Every hi, every
bye, every I love you you've ever said
Cause all of the small things that you
do are what remind me what I felt
for you And when we're apart and I'm
missing you I close my eyes and all
I see is you And the small things
you do When
we're apart and I'm missing you I close
my eyes and all I see is you
And when we're apart and I'm missing you
I close my eyes and all I see
is you Cause all of the small things
that you do are what remind me what
I felt for you And when we're apart
and I'm missing you I close my eyes
and all I see is you And the
small things you do Oh,
the small things you do