(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) I am
not the only traveller Who's not repaid his
debt I've been searching for a trail to
follow again Take me back to the night
we met And that I can't tell myself
What the hell I'm supposed to do And
that I can't tell myself Not to ride
along with you I had all and then
most of you summin' down Take me back
to the night we met I don't know
what I'm supposed to do Caught in my
destiny Well, take me back to the night
we met When the night was full of
terror And your eyes were filled with tears
When you had not touched me yet Oh,
take me back to the night we met
I had all and then most of you
summin' down Take me back to the night
we met I don't know what I'm supposed
to do Caught in my destiny Well, take
me back to the night we met