(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Georgia, right in the eye of the morning
Hurt you, in my arms you let me
Hold you, I'll never let you go again
Like I did, or used to say I
would never fall in love again until I
found her I said I would never fall
in love since you, I've fallen too I
was lost within the darkness but then I
found her, I found you Georgia,
pulled me in, I asked to love her
Once again you fell, I caught a chill
I'll never let you go again like I
did, or used to say I would never
fall in love again until I found her
I said I would never fall in love
since you, I've fallen too I was lost
within the darkness but then I found her,
I found you I
would never fall in love again until I
found her I said I would never fall
in love since you, I've fallen too I
was lost within the darkness but then I
found her, I found you