(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) 🎵 Music 🎵 🎵 I could
stare like watching stars 🎵 🎵 I could
walk you by 🎵 🎵 And I'll tell
without a thought 🎵 🎵 You'd be mine,
would you mind 🎵 🎵 If I took
your hand tonight 🎵 🎵 Know you're all
that I want this time 🎵 🎵 I'll
imagine you fell in love 🎵 🎵 I'll
love under moonlight skies with you 🎵 🎵
I think I'll picture us there with my
wings 🎵 🎵 The ocean's colours on your
face 🎵 🎵 I'll leave my heart with
your air 🎵 🎵 So let me fly
with you 🎵 🎵 Will you be forever
with me 🎵 🎵 Music
🎵 🎵
My
love will always stay by you 🎵 🎵
I'll keep it safe so don't you worry
thing 🎵 🎵 I'll tell you I love
you more 🎵 🎵 It's stuck with you
forever 🎵 🎵 So promise you won't let
it go 🎵 🎵 I'll trust the universe
will always bring me to you 🎵 🎵
I'll imagine you fell in love 🎵 🎵
I'll love under moonlight skies with you 🎵
🎵 I think I'll picture us there with
my wings 🎵 🎵 The ocean's colours on
your face 🎵 🎵 I'll leave my heart
with your air 🎵 🎵 So let me
fly with you 🎵 🎵 Will you be
forever with me 🎵
🎵
Music 🎵