(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) 🎵 Music 🎵 🎵 Maybe it's the way
you say my name 🎵 🎵 Maybe it's
the way you play your game 🎵 🎵
But it's so good 🎵 🎵 I've never
known anybody like you 🎵 🎵 But it's
so good 🎵 🎵 I've never dreamed of
nobody like you 🎵 🎵 And I've heard
of a love that comes once in a
lifetime 🎵 🎵 And I'm pretty sure that
you are that love of mine 🎵 🎵
Cause I'm in a field of glamour lies
🎵 🎵 Wishing on everyone that you'd be
mine 🎵 🎵 My next 🎵 🎵 I
see forever in your eyes 🎵 🎵 I
feel okay when I see you smile 🎵
🎵 Smile 🎵 🎵 Wishing on dandelions all
of the time 🎵 🎵 Praying to God
that one day you'll be mine 🎵 🎵
Wishing on dandelions all of the time 🎵
🎵 All of the time 🎵 🎵 I
think that you are the one for me
🎵 🎵 Cause it gets so hard to
breathe 🎵 🎵 When you're looking at me
🎵 🎵 I've never felt so alive and
free 🎵 🎵 When you're looking at me
🎵 🎵 I've never felt so happy 🎵
🎵 And I've heard of a love that
comes once in a lifetime 🎵 🎵 And
I'm pretty sure that you are that love
of mine 🎵 🎵 Cause I'm in a
field of glamour lies 🎵 🎵 Wishing on
everyone that you'd be mine 🎵 🎵 Mine
🎵 🎵 I see forever in your eyes
🎵 🎵 I feel okay when I see
you smile 🎵 🎵 Smile 🎵 🎵 Wishing
on dandelions all of the time 🎵 🎵
Praying to God that one day you'll be
mine 🎵 🎵 Wishing on dandelions all of
the time 🎵 🎵 All of the time
🎵 🎵 Dandelion into the wind you go
🎵 🎵 Won't you let my darling know
that 🎵 🎵 I'm in a field of
dandelions 🎵 🎵 Wishing on everyone that you'd
be mine 🎵 🎵 Mine 🎵 🎵 I
see forever in your eyes 🎵 🎵 I
feel okay when I see you smile 🎵
🎵 Smile 🎵 🎵 Smile 🎵 🎵 Wishing
on dandelions all of the time 🎵 🎵
Praying to God that one day you'll be
mine 🎵 🎵 Wishing on dandelions all of
the time 🎵 🎵 All of the time
🎵 🎵 I'm in a field of dandelions
🎵 🎵 Wishing on everyone that you'd be
mine 🎵 🎵 Mine 🎵