(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) They say the holy water's watered down And
this town lost in its faith The colours
will fade, eventually So if our time is
running out Day after day We'll make the
mundane a masterpiece Oh my my, oh my
my love I take one look at you,
you're taking me out Of the ordinary I
want you laying me down So we're dead
and buried Only each of you and I
Stay a trick on your fight The angels
up in the clouds Are jealous knowing we're
falling Something so wild Of the ordinary You
got me kissing the ground Of your sanctuary
Shining me with your touch Oh lord, return
me to dust The angels up in the
clouds Are jealous knowing we're falling Hopeless heart
In this sight of heaven's gate And take
my breath away At your altar, I will
pray You're the sculptor, I'm the clay Oh
my my, you're taking me out Of the
ordinary I want you laying me down So
we're dead and buried Only each of you
and I Stay a trick on your fight
The angels up in the clouds Are jealous
knowing we're falling Something so wild Of the
ordinary You got me kissing the ground Of
your sanctuary Shining me with your touch Oh
lord, return me to dust The angels up
in the clouds Are jealous knowing we're falling
Something so heavenly Higher than ecstasy Whenever you're
next to me Oh my my Ripples in
black and white Until I see your light
I thought you had to die to find
Something so wild Of the ordinary Laying me
down So we're dead and buried Jealous
knowing we're falling Something so wild Of the
ordinary You got me kissing the ground Of
your sanctuary Shining me with your touch Oh
lord, return me to dust The angels up
in the clouds Are jealous knowing we're falling